<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-10-28T17:43:42-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Haolin Yuan</title><subtitle>the profile of an engineer, researcher and software developer</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Practical Blind Membership Inference Attack via Differential Comparisons</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Practical Blind Membership Inference Attack via Differential Comparisons" /><published>2020-09-02T16:21:59-04:00</published><updated>2020-09-02T16:21:59-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/venue</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/">&lt;p&gt;We propose an MI attack, called BLINDMI, which probes the target model and extracts membership semantics via a novel approach, called differential comparison. The high-level idea is that BLINDMI first generates a dataset with nonmembers via transforming existing samples into new, and then differentially moves samples from a target dataset to the generated, non-member set in an iterative manner. If the differential move of a sample increases the set distance, BLINDMI considers the sample as non-member and vice versa. BLINDMI solve the problem that formal heavily depend on shadow models.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Haolin Yuan</name></author><category term="research" /><summary type="html">We propose an MI attack, called BLINDMI, which probes the target model and extracts membership semantics via a novel approach, called differential comparison. The high-level idea is that BLINDMI first generates a dataset with nonmembers via transforming existing samples into new, and then differentially moves samples from a target dataset to the generated, non-member set in an iterative manner. If the differential move of a sample increases the set distance, BLINDMI considers the sample as non-member and vice versa. BLINDMI solve the problem that formal heavily depend on shadow models.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">WebAlly - A case study of Web-task friend sourcing in solving CAPTCHA</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="WebAlly - A case study of Web-task friend sourcing in solving CAPTCHA" /><published>2020-07-28T16:21:59-04:00</published><updated>2020-07-28T16:21:59-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/venue</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/">&lt;p&gt;We designed and tested a proof-of-concept system called WebAlly, using Google reCAPTCHA as the task in a study with 10 pairs of a PVI adult and a friend or family member (18 in total).
We found that while WebAlly with friendsourcing requires interdependence, PVIs prefer it over using other time-consuming or low success-rate solutions, 
and expressed wanting to have WebAlly with crowdsourcing as a backup alternative. 
As for compensation, participants generally tend to compensate the helpers but have their own preferences in how to compensate. Participants also found that WebAlly did well in task performance and protecting their privacy and security. 
In addition, we found that WebAlly had a positive impact on their social relationship with the helpers&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Haolin Yuan</name></author><category term="research" /><summary type="html">We designed and tested a proof-of-concept system called WebAlly, using Google reCAPTCHA as the task in a study with 10 pairs of a PVI adult and a friend or family member (18 in total). We found that while WebAlly with friendsourcing requires interdependence, PVIs prefer it over using other time-consuming or low success-rate solutions, and expressed wanting to have WebAlly with crowdsourcing as a backup alternative. As for compensation, participants generally tend to compensate the helpers but have their own preferences in how to compensate. Participants also found that WebAlly did well in task performance and protecting their privacy and security. In addition, we found that WebAlly had a positive impact on their social relationship with the helpers</summary></entry></feed>